The oil and sales of the segment, which
can be in action today on the basis of news, perhaps
with us in the Trimurti segment, good morning
Shraddha, tell me,
your newspaper will be in focus,
here the P firm Advent
International Atlantic is closing,
in the stock sale of Burger King, Everstone
's nearly 41% tax holding is
going on in New Delhi, HDFC will also be in focus,
here Bearing Equity can probably
buy 90% stake
in Credila Financial Services, whose
valuation can be from ₹10,000 to ₹12,000 crores
and remember this company which
is the educational loan of HDFC and this deal is
before June, it is the power before this, apart from this
ICC Lombard will also be in focus and if you
look here, ICC Bank is
more than 50%, almost 48% right now, okay, now
that Kar Person Tech is a bigger power, now
what will be its impact, its overall impact will be, the
overhang of 18% sale of stock
sale has been gone and this is the positive
reaction  It can be seen in group companies
and the third company will be
Vandana Spurti in Fox. Ganga
Ready here has to resign from her non-ex
YouTube director post and she
requested the company to
classify her promoter status
and there was an exclusive of 18 and Swadesh
where he was in talks
with potential bankers where he
can sell his stake or block
deals. Now remember, he has almost 14.6%
holding in the company right now. To
tell us all these stocks, but
keep this last stop in mind
because whenever this classify happens,
any promoter can take a big block and
once the block is taken, there will be no supply. The
numbers in the stock were good and our news is
that
Residents Tech
wants to take this 14%.
After that this interest will not stop because
after this there will be a big supply,
hence there is
definitely a market demand, let's do something else.